<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gladys Fang</title>
    <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gladys Fang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 23:29:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tiger-pillow.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #2 - Research</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 23:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in doing research at the undergraduate level, read on! I had many pitfalls to write this guide for you.
My experience with different labs Disclaimer: I have nothing bad to say about the following professors (except Van Tessel perhaps). My experience /time spent in each lab doesn&amp;rsquo;t even qualify me to judge in most cases. I left because incompatibility and my own problems &amp;ndash; see reflections later on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gladys&#39; Favorite Resorts Ranked, 2020-21</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/snowboard_resorts_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/snowboard_resorts_review/</guid>
      <description>Snowboarded for 50 days this season. Wish I could say this every year. Here are the reviews!   Winter Park/ Mary Jane  Best tree runs! Practically skiable everywhere, good food, and Eagle Wind if you got lucky.    Snowbird Steep, Scary but So Much Fun!    Aspen Highlands
Personally I love hard workouts, and nothing beats the hike up Highland bowl. Awesome trees, that chair was slow though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/aboutpage/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 23:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/aboutpage/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
I am Gladys.
I am interested in Evolutionry Biology. I graduated from Yale College in 2021. I will be attending Ecole Polytechnique de Lausanne in September 2021.
Some other things that I do include: snowboarding/skiing, guitar, hiking, trail running, figure skating, badminton. I code, take some photos and write a bit.
You can contact me at gladysfangcs dot gmail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #1 - Courses</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:36:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</guid>
      <description>I have two finals left, yet I decide to write about my Yale experience. After all, what&amp;rsquo;s more legitimate than procrastinating by reflecting?
I majored in Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) at Yale. My grades are mediocre, and I have never been inducted in any honorary society or organizations. I am by no means among &amp;ldquo;the bright&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the hardworking&amp;rdquo; ones at Yale, and very much just an ordinary international student struggling on a day-to-day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>