<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gladys Fang&#39;s Stuff</title>
    <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gladys Fang&#39;s Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:31:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tiger-pillow.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>边上学，边开车横穿美国</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/drivingacrossus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:31:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/drivingacrossus/</guid>
      <description>本文流水账，长度约等于New Haven到Seattle的距离。
上个秋天自己的状态非常糟糕，虽然没有影响我学习和申请研究生的结果，但是自己是不开心的。我租的房子很便宜，所以阳光不怎么好。纽黑文大大小小的街道也全都跑遍了，时间长了，便觉得乏味。
我内心一直向往着 On the Road 或者 Into the Wild 里面那样的年轻人。我想像Jack Kerouac 和 Christopher McCandless那样生活。我想去大西部，去到未知，流浪的日子。如果我是美国公民，又没有什么经济压力，那我必然选择成为一名dirtbag，用最便宜的方式活在自然的中间，社会的边缘。写出来觉得自己很搞笑，我可真理想主义。每天读书，开车，攀岩，爬山，睡在星空下泥土上。我厌烦了耶鲁的精英主义, credentialism, 互联网黑话和处处的焦虑。
于是我2020年9月底第一次产生了离开的想法。我想在路上，往西边开，一路开到雪场，然后在那里度过一个年轻人应该有的冬天。想法我酝酿了一下，好像可以完成，就跟母亲打了个招呼。母亲很是鼓励我，说想让我多出去看看，就是要注意安全。
10月份11月份很忙很忙。我准备GRE，每天花4个小时收集实验数据，准备grad school申请，要推荐信，还上着一门关于犹太人大屠杀的课。买车是这一切之上的压力。短平快的买了辆2017年的Honda Pilot，差不多就行。之所以买辆这么大的车，是因为我想每天晚上找一个沃尔玛停车场，住在车上，省钱。
11月25日我跟朋友吃过感恩节晚餐后，26号一大早就出发了。第一天沿着I-80，开了5个小时车，到了Pennsylvania 的一个小镇 Clearfield。我这一路并没提前安排，基本开累了就找个小宾馆睡下。住的地方都很便宜，Redfin一晚上40$，只是有些破的吓人，门缝有我大拇指那么宽，不用开门都能看见外面。
11月27日穿过Ohio,Indiana和Illinois, 来到了密歇根湖胖的Chesterton，住了一晚上。在同一座楼睡的都是大卡车司机，16轮全拖挂的货车在停车场一排排。醒来之后面对的是荒郊野地，司机们早就走了，我也上路了。
11月30日来到了Iowa的Des Moines，住了三天，还在附近的公园里跑了跑步。之所以停下来是有点开累了，加上要做presentation和写paper。我没怎么探索这个城市，但我还是要感慨为什么有人会愿意住在这里。疫情原因，更是空城一座，有点像Grand Theft Auto游戏里面的那种城市，偶尔街边一两个人，办公楼的玻璃都干净锃亮，完全没有diversity，不是白人就是黑人。这个城市没有优秀的美术馆和音乐，没有山野和云间，不知道那里的人是如何生活的。
我出发之前最担心的事情，就是能不能完成耶鲁的课业和研究生申请。但令我惊奇的是，出发之后，我效率惊人，到Clearfield的第一天晚上就写完了自己文书的初稿。在路上，生活变得很简单也很空旷。开车的时候，脑子是半放空的状态，便可以用来想文书的结构，想自己过往的经历，跟自己对话。想烦了，就调出来Taylor Swift的歌单，大声的跟着唱&amp;quot;you belong with me~&amp;rdquo;。到了旅店，收拾好东西洗完澡，变坐下来一股脑的干完活。为了省钱，吃的也很简单，一天三顿都是peanut butter + rice cake。
开车的就是要放空，只听歌，不要audio book一类的。
离开了Iowa,又到了Nebraska州的North Platte住了一晚，然后再Wyoming首府Cheyenne住了一晚，终于到了我所爱的小城 &amp;ndash; Park City，Utah。这一路35小时，开了大概7天。本来想着在路上玩一玩，但耶鲁的压力还是在身上，完全没有心情。
Park City就是我所想象的模样 &amp;ndash; 富裕，安全，景色到极致的滑雪小镇，在盐湖城旁边30分钟就能开到。如果圣诞老人不住在阿拉斯加，他大概会住在这里吧。 我很幸运，11月份就定了一个合适的airbnb，很便宜又很舒适。自己吃的很好，拉开窗帘就能看到远处的Park City Ski Resort，一条条雪道在召唤我。明明知道很多事情要做，我还是第二天就跑去Snowbird，开启了这个雪季的第一天。
就这样我从美国东岸开到了落基山脉旁。
在Park City我就一直在准备申请材料和期末考试了，压力还是很大的。好在一个人住，不开心了就下楼溜达一圈。Utah的冬天冷的骇人，但是我喜欢，空气格外的的清爽干净。有时候还去旁边的山上跑步，开始了自己的 trail running尝试。
我很幸运，找到了一群朋友，12月中旬来盐湖城加入我。早上7点起赶第一班缆车，滑到下午4点最后一班缆车，不情愿的回到城里，去Laan Na买上一大份pad see ew，然后4个人一起蜷缩在电视机前面看着Netflix吃饭。这是一场well-earned闲散。
在盐湖城Big Cottonwood Canyon和Little Cottonwood Canyon滑够了之后，我们就顺着I-70公路南下到了Aspen，来到了世界著名的滑雪胜地。Snowmass用一场9inch的大雪迎接我们，尝到了什么叫科罗拉多的干粉。我那时候水平已有十足的进步，小树林也是畅通无阻。
很不幸，我在1月1日元旦当天去了Buttermilk，跳一个小跳台的时候没有落稳，把右肩膀摔脱臼了。肩膀自从打羽毛球的时候就有rotator cuff torn，而这次摔得太严重了。我每天都半夜疼醒，坐在床上好一会儿，把右胳膊调到合适的位置，然后再躺下身去，祈祷自己不会再次疼醒。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #5 - Pieces of Yale (photos)</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 11:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</guid>
      <description>To write this, I scrolled through my photos with great fondness. Here are some pieces.
Yale is just mesmerizing in Summer.
The marble wall of the Beinecke Library Rainbow over the Harkness Tower
Typical D-hall
Winter chubbiness
Discrete math?
From my window, sophomore year
The Harvard-Yale game
Hillhouse Ave in the Fall
Bluebird day from Malone
Old campus through teary eyes
Packing for home
Snow, 2020
with lots of love,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #4 - Mindset Problems</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 07:01:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</guid>
      <description>Some content that have helped me tremendously in getting through Yale at tough times.
Some quotes on fashion  &amp;ldquo;Fashion, by the way, is commerce masquerading as hip. I&amp;rsquo;m not at all interested in fashion, which is why I rarely buy new clothes. The fact that fashion goes out of fashion and then comes back into fashion based solely on what a few people sometime think they can sell, well to me, that&amp;rsquo;s insanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #3 - Relationships</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 06:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</guid>
      <description>The juicy part! Except mine isn&amp;rsquo;t really juicy.
Friendships To be perfectly honest I had always struggled making friends or maintaining friendships, and especially at Yale. After four years, I have gotten to know some people (I am an acquitance with maybe 5% of my class), and call maybe half a dozen people &amp;ldquo;friends&amp;rdquo;, and have two people who I talk to frequently enough.
I long for the kind of &amp;ldquo;I will always be there for you&amp;rdquo; friendship, as depicted in movies or books, the kind between Harry Ron and Hermione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #2 - Research</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 23:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in doing research at the undergraduate level, read on! I had many pitfalls to write this guide for you.
My experience with different labs Disclaimer: I have nothing bad to say about the following professors (except Van Tessel perhaps). My experience /time spent in each lab doesn&amp;rsquo;t even qualify me to judge in most cases. I left because incompatibility and my own problems &amp;ndash; see reflections later on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/aboutme/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 23:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/aboutme/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
I am Gladys.
I am interested in Evolutionry Biology. I graduated from Yale College in 2021. I will be attending Ecole Polytechnique de Lausanne in September 2021.
Some other things that I do include: snowboarding/skiing, guitar, hiking, trail running, figure skating, badminton. I code, take some photos and write a bit.
You can contact me at gladysfangcs dot gmail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #1 - Courses</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:36:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</guid>
      <description>I have two finals left, yet I decide to write about my Yale experience. After all, what&amp;rsquo;s more legitimate than procrastinating by reflecting?
I majored in Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) at Yale. My grades are mediocre, and I have never been inducted in any honorary society or organizations. I am by no means among &amp;ldquo;the bright&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the hardworking&amp;rdquo; ones at Yale, and very much just an ordinary international student struggling on a day-to-day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski/Snowboard Resorts Ranked, 2020-21</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/snowboard_resorts_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 11:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/snowboard_resorts_review/</guid>
      <description>Snowboarded for 50 days this season. Wish I could say this every year. Here are the reviews!   Winter Park/ Mary Jane  Best tree runs! Practically skiable everywhere, good food, and Eagle Wind if you got lucky.    Snowbird Steep, Scary but So Much Fun!    Aspen Highlands
Personally I love hard workouts, and nothing beats the hike up Highland bowl. Awesome trees, that chair was slow though.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>