<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yale on Gladys Fang&#39;s Stuff</title>
    <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/yale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yale on Gladys Fang&#39;s Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 11:36:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/yale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #5 - Pieces of Yale (photos)</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 11:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</guid>
      <description>To write this, I scrolled through my photos with great fondness. Here are some pieces.
Yale is just mesmerizing in Summer.
The marble wall of the Beinecke Library Rainbow over the Harkness Tower
Typical D-hall
Winter chubbiness
Discrete math?
From my window, sophomore year
The Harvard-Yale game
Hillhouse Ave in the Fall
Bluebird day from Malone
Old campus through teary eyes
Packing for home
Snow, 2020
with lots of love,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #4 - Mindset Problems</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 07:01:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</guid>
      <description>Some content that have helped me tremendously in getting through Yale at tough times.
Some quotes on fashion  &amp;ldquo;Fashion, by the way, is commerce masquerading as hip. I&amp;rsquo;m not at all interested in fashion, which is why I rarely buy new clothes. The fact that fashion goes out of fashion and then comes back into fashion based solely on what a few people sometime think they can sell, well to me, that&amp;rsquo;s insanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #3 - Relationships</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 06:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</guid>
      <description>The juicy part! Except mine isn&amp;rsquo;t really juicy.
Friendships To be perfectly honest I had always struggled making friends or maintaining friendships, and especially at Yale. After four years, I have gotten to know some people (I am an acquitance with maybe 5% of my class), and call maybe half a dozen people &amp;ldquo;friends&amp;rdquo;, and have two people who I talk to frequently enough.
I long for the kind of &amp;ldquo;I will always be there for you&amp;rdquo; friendship, as depicted in movies or books, the kind between Harry Ron and Hermione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #2 - Research</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 23:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in doing research at the undergraduate level, read on! I had many pitfalls to write this guide for you.
My experience with different labs Disclaimer: I have nothing bad to say about the following professors (except Van Tessel perhaps). My experience /time spent in each lab doesn&amp;rsquo;t even qualify me to judge in most cases. I left because incompatibility and my own problems &amp;ndash; see reflections later on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #1 - Courses</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:36:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</guid>
      <description>I have two finals left, yet I decide to write about my Yale experience. After all, what&amp;rsquo;s more legitimate than procrastinating by reflecting?
I majored in Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) at Yale. My grades are mediocre, and I have never been inducted in any honorary society or organizations. I am by no means among &amp;ldquo;the bright&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the hardworking&amp;rdquo; ones at Yale, and very much just an ordinary international student struggling on a day-to-day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>