<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yale on Yiyuan Fang&#39;s Stuff</title>
    <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/yale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yale on Yiyuan Fang&#39;s Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 20:09:38 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/yale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>触摸这座城的每条街道 -- New Haven跑步指南</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/runninginnewhaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 20:09:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/runninginnewhaven/</guid>
      <description>纽黑文以两件事著名：耶鲁和高犯罪率。具体犯罪率有多高我很难说一个准确数字，但的确三天两头收到学校armed robbery, bulgary, sexual harassement的邮件警告，还是很吓人的。
但纽黑文这座城市还是比较适合跑步的。我四年下来在纽黑文可能跑过上千公里，在这里列举几条常跑的线路，给要搬到这里的朋友们一个小小指南。这些路线均从Grove St和College St的交界处开始和结束，实际情况可能需要大家自己调整。整个East Rock地区也相对安全，只要避免Dixwell西侧，Amistad 南侧，Orange的东侧，自己提高警惕就不会有太大问题（我四年基本每周跑4-5回，没有遇到过令我害怕的事情）。还是建议大家带上手机，不要闯红绿灯。
有些人会抱怨美国的生活单调而三点一线 &amp;ndash; 食堂，实验室，宿舍。我会说：出去跑跑步吧，看看这个城市。跑的多了就对这个小城的每条街道有一种特殊的感觉 &amp;ndash; 哪个院子里种了桃子，哪个街角有玉兰花，谁家房子有着漂亮的French Window &amp;ndash; 都记在心里。跑者也大多友善，见面会说morning，会互相微笑点头，也是一种鼓励。小城的春夏秋冬，阴雨风晴都历历在目。一个音乐家有着更灵敏的耳朵，能听出和弦细微的变化和鼓点的精巧设计。一个小镇跑者对这个城也更加敏感，闭上眼睛都能回想起一个街角的样子，能感受到春夏秋冬的温度湿度。跑者会觉得纽黑文变小了 &amp;ndash; East Rock也没有那么远嘛，Lighthouse 也可以跑过去的。同时她又会觉得纽黑文变大了 &amp;ndash; 每条道路都载着无数的细节，心情和时光。
1. East Rock Summit: &amp;ndash; 我最喜欢的路线 长度： 5miles +
难度： 7/10
危险程度： 3/10
路线描述： Orange St跑到头后右拐，进入English Drive旁边的trail，右手靠河，左手靠马路，非常优美。在看到棒球场（一大片草坪）之后左转，跑上柏油路，然后就沿着柏油路一路向上就可以。1.5mile之后遇到一个红色的围栏，从围栏两侧过去后左拐继续向上，再有1mile即可达到East Rock Summit。如果晚上6点以前去的话基本上能看到1-2个人，周末人更多。
亮点： 野生动物，除了常见的花栗鼠，松鼠以外，还可以经常看到鹿，各类鸟。
注意： 此条路线有较高的提升（将近300米左右），跑上坡对于大部分没有经验的跑着会非常痛苦，是很好的训练。除非跑的很快或者天气很凉，否则建议带一小瓶（300ml即可）的水。
2. Med School Loop: &amp;ndash; 可以people watch的路线 长度： 5miles +
难度： 5/10
危险程度： 7/10
路线描述： 穿过耶鲁的中心Cross Campus后左转，沿着York St一路向南跑。跑到George St会遇到Walgreens，从桥下穿过后继续向前。跑到Medical School旁边后，左转进入Cedar St，继续向前路过Blue State Coffee和Amistad Park, 然后在校园最南端的Amistad Building前左转。如果累了可以去Amistad Park小坐一下，这里是耶鲁少有的没有流浪汉的公园，非常新和干净。沿Amistad St跑200米后左转，进入Gold St，左手边是新开的luxury apartments，之后再左转，从Yale Psychiatry Hopsital旁路过，回到College St, 沿College St向北跑。这是可以选择一路沿College St更快的回到校园中心，或者沿着George St右转800米后跑到Orange St上，再沿着Orange St向北。 亮点： orange st上有许多可爱的小商店和餐厅，看看橱窗就会很开心。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #5 - Pieces of Yale (photos)</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 11:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection5/</guid>
      <description>To write this, I scrolled through my photos with great fondness. Here are some pieces.
Yale is just mesmerizing in Summer.
The marble wall of the Beinecke Library Rainbow over the Harkness Tower
Typical D-hall
Winter chubbiness
Discrete math?
From my window, sophomore year
The Harvard-Yale game
Hillhouse Ave in the Fall
Bluebird day from Malone
Old campus through teary eyes
Packing for home
Snow, 2020
with lots of love,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #4 - Mindset Problems</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 07:01:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection4/</guid>
      <description>Some content that have helped me tremendously in getting through Yale at tough times.
Some quotes on fashion  &amp;ldquo;Fashion, by the way, is commerce masquerading as hip. I&amp;rsquo;m not at all interested in fashion, which is why I rarely buy new clothes. The fact that fashion goes out of fashion and then comes back into fashion based solely on what a few people sometime think they can sell, well to me, that&amp;rsquo;s insanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #3 - Relationships</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 06:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection3/</guid>
      <description>The juicy part! Except mine isn&amp;rsquo;t really juicy.
Friendships To be perfectly honest I had always struggled making friends or maintaining friendships, and especially at Yale. After four years, I have gotten to know some people (I am an acquitance with maybe 5% of my class), and call maybe half a dozen people &amp;ldquo;friends&amp;rdquo;, and have two people who I talk to frequently enough.
I long for the kind of &amp;ldquo;I will always be there for you&amp;rdquo; friendship, as depicted in movies or books, the kind between Harry Ron and Hermione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #2 - Research</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 23:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection2/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in doing research at the undergraduate level, read on! I had many pitfalls to write this guide for you.
My experience with different labs Disclaimer: I have nothing bad to say about the following professors (except Van Tessel perhaps). My experience /time spent in each lab doesn&amp;rsquo;t even qualify me to judge in most cases. I left because incompatibility and my own problems &amp;ndash; see reflections later on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Reflections #1 - Courses</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:36:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/reflection1/</guid>
      <description>I have two finals left, yet I decide to write about my Yale experience. After all, what&amp;rsquo;s more legitimate than procrastinating by reflecting?
I majored in Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) at Yale. My grades are mediocre, and I have never been inducted in any honorary society or organizations. I am by no means among &amp;ldquo;the bright&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the hardworking&amp;rdquo; ones at Yale, and very much just an ordinary international student struggling on a day-to-day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
