<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Readings on Yiyuan Fang&#39;s Stuff</title>
    <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/readings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Readings on Yiyuan Fang&#39;s Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:18:45 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tiger-pillow.github.io/categories/readings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Reading Records </title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/2023reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/2023reading/</guid>
      <description>1. The Escape Artist by Jonathan Freeland Enticing story beautifully told, devoured it in three days.
2. An Immense World by Ed Gave up half way through, gonna retry with a paperback (the pictures of animals mentioned are much needed!)
3. 欧洲文明十五讲 15 Lectures of European Civilization - 陈乐民 Lecture notes of Prof. Chen at Pekin Uni, very well written overview of European History
4. Tu peut-être en parler à quelqu&amp;rsquo;un par Lori Gottlier [Maybe You Should Talk to Someone] Read the French translation of it, funny, interesting, wasn&amp;rsquo;t convinced though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 2022 Reading Records </title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/2022reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 21:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/2022reading/</guid>
      <description>How delightful are those fresh, untouched pages!
The pleasure of reading is multiplied during exam periods. Everything seems fun when compared to reviewing(alas how I started this blog!) So here I am, happy to be back with 2022&amp;rsquo;s reading record.
I like both fiction and non-fiction. Non-fiction is not immediately &amp;ldquo;useful&amp;rdquo;,and thus it is looked-down by some of my more career-oriented acquitances. But it teaches us so much about life. Biographies and history are bounded by the limits of real events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passages that I enjoy</title>
      <link>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/recentquotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:40:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tiger-pillow.github.io/post/recentquotes/</guid>
      <description>I sometimes find my words lacking the power, the forcefulness that my emotions carry, so out of laziness, I borrow others&#39; words. These are some recent ones.
On dressing up for the male gaze (from Neapolitan Novels)  In recent years I had begun to be interested in fashion, to educate my taste under Adele&amp;rsquo;s guidance, and now I enjoyed dressing up. But sometimes &amp;ndash; especially when I had dressed not only to make a good impression in general but for a man &amp;ndash; preparing myself (this was the word) seemed to me to have something ridiculous about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
